Thank you for noticing!
(Sheldon:)No, I mean it. I mean it.
(Sheldon:)It's like you have
the soul of a label maker.
(Amy:)You know what I
love about you?
(Sheldon:)Hmm?
(Stuart:)You never leave the house
without a paper clip!
(Sheldon:)You never know
when two pieces of paper
(Sheldon:)might temporarily need fastening
in the top left corner.
(Stuart:)I also love how you
never use swear words.
(Sheldon:)You know, it turns out,
(Sheldon:)you can hurt people
just as well without 'em.
(Amy:)Maybe I can get a little help
putting some of this stuff away.
(Sheldon:)Oh, calm down.
(Sheldon:)I already put away
five of these!
(Sheldon:)You see?
(Sheldon:)No muss, no fuss,
not a single cuss.